https://ahdionline.site-ym.com/privacy.aspx

Association for Healthcare Documentation Integrity
Search »
Home   |   About AHDI   |   Shopping Cart   |   Contact Us   |   Sign In   |   Join
Access Your Benefits
Individual Professional MembersStudent & Postgraduate MembersCorporate & Educational MembersSustaining Members
Volunteer OpportunitiesAHDI MeetingsAHDI ExchangeRecognitionHDI WeekSR Errors
Certification
Why Get Certified?Types of Credentials
RHDSCHDS
Exam PreparationSign Up for an ExamRecertification
RHDS RecertificationCHDS/CMT RecertificationCHDS Bridge Course (for CMTs)Retiring Your Credentials
Credentialing Commission
Body of Knowledge
Book of Style & StandardsBest Practices
Documentation Style & StandardsCompensationCopy and PasteDocument CreationElectronic Health RecordsQuality AssuranceSpeech Recognition TechnologyTurnaround Time
HIPAA ComplianceSurvey ReportsWorkforce Development
CompensationIndustry SurveysMedical Transcription ClassificationModel Job DescriptionsNew-Hire Test PrepU.S. Regulations
Learning
Online Learning LibraryAnnual Conference
HDIVC20Conference ScheduleExhibitor ListConference FAQsPast Conferences
Plexus e-magazineTraining Courses
Mastering the EHR CourseSpeciality CoursesAcute Care ModuleRHDS Study CourseCHDS Study CourseRHDS Recredentialing CourseCHDS Bridge Course (for CMTs)
Live WebinarsRecordings on DemandProductsAHDI ExchangeFind an Approved ProgramFor Educators & Schools
Education Approval ProgramPreapproval ProgramEducators Alliance
Your Career
Career CenterBecome an MT/HDSFind an Approved ProgramCareer MapCareer ResourcesOWLS Academy
Advocacy & Policy
About AHDIWhere We StandAdvocacy AgendaYour Record Speaks
SR Errors
HDI WeekPress Room
Store
Shop NowProduct GuideOnline Buyers GuideAdvertise, Exhibit, & Sponsor
Privacy Policy/Legal
Updated 5/24/2018
Privacy Statement
AHDI is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the AHDI website and governs data collection and usage. By using the AHDI website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
AHDI collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address, or telephone number. AHDI also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, job role, and work setting.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by AHDI. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by AHDI for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the AHDI Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through AHDI public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: AHDI does not read any of your private online communications.
AHDI encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from AHDI so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. AHDI is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the AHDI and AHDI family of websites.
Use of your Personal Information
As part of a membership, purchase, subscription, or registration agreement, members and registrants will be contacted by us through mail, email, and/or phone to communicate with them about their membership, purchase, and/or registration. They will be contacted for renewal, surveys, updates concerning their account profile, and special offers related to their membership, purchase, and/or registration. We also use the information to contact them for marketing purposes. Members/customers are provided with the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from AHDI. You may contact AHDI to update your preferences or simply click the opt-out link on the bottom of any AHDI email.
AHDI may contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (email, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the external business partner. In addition, AHDI may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to AHDI, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. Members/customers of AHDI may opt out of third-party mailings at any time. When logged into the website, you can manage your preferences by going to “Manage Profile.” An opt-out option is available at the bottom of all emails or you can contact AHDI at ahdi@ahdionline.org or 800-982-2182 to have your record updated.
AHDI does not collect sensitive personal information such as race, religion, or political affiliations. Information such as passwords and credit card numbers are never disclosed in any form to any outside party.
AHDI keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within AHDI, in order to determine what AHDI services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within AHDI to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
AHDI websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with a legal process served on AHDI or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AHDI; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AHDI or the public.
Use of Cookies
The AHDI website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize AHDI pages, or register with the AHDI site or services, a cookie helps AHDI to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same AHDI website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the AHDI features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the AHDI services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
AHDI secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. AHDI secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
AHDI will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. AHDI encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how AHDI is protecting your information.
Contact Information
AHDI welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that AHDI has not adhered to this Statement, please contact AHDI at webmaster@ahdionline.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Terms of Use
Agreement Between User and AHDI
The AHDI website is comprised of various web pages operated by AHDI.
The AHDI website is offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein. Your use of the AHDI website constitutes your agreement to all such terms, conditions, and notices.
Modification of These Terms of Use
AHDI reserves the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices under which the AHDI website is offered, including but not limited to the charges associated with the use of the AHDI website.
Links to Third Party Sites
The AHDI website may contain links to other websites ("Linked Sites"). The Linked Sites are not under the control of AHDI and AHDI is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. AHDI is not responsible for webcasting or any other form of transmission received from any Linked Site. AHDI is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by AHDI of the site or any association with its operators.
Copyright and Trademark Notices
All content of the AHDI website is powered by YourMembership.com and/or its suppliers. All rights reserved.
Copyright Policy
The contents of all material available on this Internet site are copyrighted by AHDI unless otherwise indicated. Copyright is not claimed as to any part of an original work prepared by a U.S. or state government officer or employee as part of that person's official duties. All rights are reserved by AHDI, and content may not be reproduced, downloaded, disseminated, published, or transferred in any form or by any means, except with the prior written permission of AHDI, or as indicated herein. Members of AHDI may download pages or other content for their own use, consistent with the mission and purpose of AHDI (as codified in its governing documents) on a single computer. However, no part of such content may be otherwise or subsequently reproduced, downloaded, disseminated, published, or transferred, in any form or by any means, except with the prior written permission of, and with express attribution to, AHDI. Copyright infringement is a violation of federal law that may subject violators to criminal and civil penalties. AHDI and the ASSOCIATION FOR HEALTHCARE DOCUMENTATION INTEGRITY are service marks of AHDI. Unless otherwise indicated, AHDI reserves the copyright on all of its materials and logos. No reprints may be made in whole or in part without the express permission of AHDI.
Trademarks
The names, trademarks, service marks, and logos of AHDI appearing on this site may not be used in any advertising or publicity, or otherwise to indicate AHDI’s sponsorship of or affiliation with any product or service, without AHDI’s prior express written permission.
Legal Notice and Disclaimer
Some information contained or linked to in AHDI's Internet site (including but not limited to information contained in any of AHDI's interactive forums) has been provided by AHDI members or nonmembers. AHDI does not endorse, approve, or certify such information, nor does it guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, timeliness, or correct sequencing of such information. Use of such information is voluntary, and reliance on it should only be undertaken after an independent review of its accuracy, completeness, efficacy, and timeliness. Reference herein to any specific commercial product, process, or service by trade name, trademark, service mark, manufacturer, or otherwise does not constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by AHDI. AHDI (including its employees and agents) assumes no responsibility for consequences resulting from the use of the information herein, (or from use of the information obtained at linked Internet addresses), or in any respect for the content of such information, including (but not limited to) errors or omissions, the accuracy or reasonableness of factual or scientific assumptions, studies or conclusions, the defamatory nature of statements, ownership of copyright or other intellectual property rights, or the violation of property, privacy, or personal rights of others. AHDI is not responsible for, and expressly disclaims all liability for, damages of any kind arising out of use, reference to, or reliance on such information. No guarantees or warranties, including (but not limited to) any express or implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular use or purpose, are made by AHDI with respect to such information.
No Unlawful or Prohibited Use
As a condition of your use of the AHDI website, you warrant to AHDI that you will not use the AHDI website for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices. You may not use the AHDI website in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the AHDI website or interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of the AHDI website. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the AHDI websites.
Use of Communication Services
The AHDI website may contain bulletin board services, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities, personal web pages, calendars, and/or other message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with the public at large or with a group (collectively, "Communication Services"), you agree to use the Communication Services only to post, send and receive messages and material that are proper and related to the particular Communication Service. By way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree that when using a Communication Service, you will not:
Defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others.
Publish, post, upload, distribute or disseminate any inappropriate, profane, defamatory, infringing, obscene, indecent or unlawful topic, name, material or information.
Upload files that contain software or other material protected by intellectual property laws (or by rights of privacy of publicity) unless you own or control the rights thereto or have received all necessary consents.
Upload files that contain viruses, corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of another's computer.
Advertise or offer to sell or buy any goods or services for any business purpose, unless such Communication Service specifically allows such messages.
Conduct or forward surveys, contests, pyramid schemes or chain letters.
Download any file posted by another user of a Communication Service that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner.
Falsify or delete any author attributions, legal or other proper notices or proprietary designations or labels of the origin or source of software or other material contained in a file that is uploaded.
Restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Communication Services.
Violate any code of conduct or other guidelines which may be applicable for any particular Communication Service.
Harvest or otherwise collect information about others, including e-mail addresses, without their consent.
Violate any applicable laws or regulations.
AHDI has no obligation to monitor the Communication Services. However, AHDI reserves the right to review materials posted to a Communication Service and to remove any materials in its sole discretion. AHDI reserves the right to terminate your access to any or all of the Communication Services at any time without notice for any reason whatsoever.
AHDI reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in AHDI's sole discretion.
Always use caution when giving out any personally identifying information about yourself or your children in any Communication Service. AHDI does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Communication Service and, therefore, AHDI specifically disclaims any liability with regard to the Communication Services and any actions resulting from your participation in any Communication Service. Managers and hosts are not authorized AHDI spokespersons, and their views do not necessarily reflect those of AHDI.
Materials uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on usage, reproduction and/or dissemination. You are responsible for adhering to such limitations if you download the materials.
Materials Provided to AHDI or Posted to Any AHDI Website
AHDI does not claim ownership of the materials you provide to AHDI (including feedback and suggestions) or post, upload, input or submit to any AHDI website or its associated services (collectively "Submissions"). However, by posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your Submission you are granting AHDI, its affiliated companies and necessary sublicensees permission to use your Submission in connection with the operation of their Internet businesses including, without limitation, the rights to: copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and reformat your Submission; and to publish your name in connection with your Submission.
No compensation will be paid with respect to the use of your Submission, as provided herein. AHDI is under no obligation to post or use any Submission you may provide and may remove any Submission at any time in AHDI's sole discretion.
By posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your Submission you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your Submission as described in this section including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the Submissions.
LIABILITY DISCLAIMER
THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THE AHDI WEBSITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. AHDI AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE AHDI WEBSITE AT ANY TIME. ADVICE RECEIVED VIA THE AHDI WEBSITE SHOULD NOT BE RELIED UPON FOR PERSONAL, MEDICAL, LEGAL OR FINANCIAL DECISIONS AND YOU SHOULD CONSULT AN APPROPRIATE PROFESSIONAL FOR SPECIFIC ADVICE TAILORED TO YOUR SITUATION.
AHDI AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS CONTAINED ON THE AHDI WEBSITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ALL SUCH INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. AHDI AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THIS INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL AHDI AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE AHDI WEBSITE, WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE AHDI WEBSITE OR RELATED SERVICES, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THE AHDI WEBSITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE AHDI WEBSITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF AHDI OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE AHDI WEBSITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE AHDI WEBSITE.
SERVICE CONTACT: webmaster@ahdionline.org
Termination/Access Restriction
AHDI reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to the AHDI website and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice. To the maximum extent permitted by law, this agreement is governed by the laws of the State of California, U.S.A. and you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in Stanislaus County, California, U.S.A. in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of the AHDI website. Use of the AHDI website is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these terms and conditions, including without limitation this paragraph. You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and AHDI as a result of this agreement or use of the AHDI website. AHDI's performance of this agreement is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in this agreement is in derogation of AHDI's right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of the AHDI website or information provided to or gathered by AHDI with respect to such use. If any part of this agreement is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations set forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of the agreement shall continue in effect. Unless otherwise specified herein, this agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the user and AHDI with respect to the AHDI website and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and AHDI with respect to the AHDI website. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. It is the express wish to the parties that this agreement and all related documents be drawn up in English.
SEARCH & CONNECT
Find a Member
Find a Credentialed Professional
Find an Approved Education Program
Find a Job
Find the AHDI Exchange
Find a Live Event
Find an Online Course
Forgot your password?Haven't registered yet?
Calendar
more
10/14/2020 » 10/17/2020AHIMA20 Virtual Conference10/19/2020AHDI Board Meeting10/21/2020"ASK AHDI"11/16/2020AHDI Board Meeting
© Copyright 1997-2020 by the Association for Healthcare Documentation Integrity. All rights reserved.
Site Map | Advertise | Legal/Privacy Policy
Association Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
